Raissa Damasceno

Sydney, Australia | +61 426485265 | raissa.dot@gmail.com | Linkedin | Github | Portfolio

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over the last year, I worked at a fast growing startup to launch multiple features that directly impact customers. Having started to learn how to code 18 months ago, I'm on a fast growing learning journey to become a world-class developer. I've participated in coding bootcamps in Portugal and in Sydney, have gone through multiple online courses, built my own personal projects and have real world experience through working at a startup. I've learned many frameworks, improved my design architecture, and deployed code to production. In my personal projects, I've focused on building projects where I could learn more about API's, HTML, CSS, Javascript and React.

SKILLS

- **Javascript**
- React
- Material UI
- **Unit Test**
- HTML

- CSS
- Bootstrap
- API
- Github
- Git

- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- Node.is
- Express.js
- AWS cloud

EXPERIENCE

YouVisa, Full Stack Developer

December 2021 - October 2022

- Building a responsive Visa Form V2, using technologies that ensure a better customer experience and scalability. Support in making improvements to the Visa Form v1 and bug fixing.
- Responsible for building a desktop robot that automates the filling of forms, helping the operations team fill out forms in bulk and providing scalability for the company.
- Support in the architecture design and elaboration of the project to create mass emails using serverless technology to help the operation team in the mass creation of registrations for customers for a greater scalability of the company.
- Responsible for fetching data from Click Up API, analyzing and converting it into data structures and storing it in the database, providing the data team with access to large sets of parsed data in real time.

CP Aduaneira, Finance Manager

November 2018 - July 2021

Responsible for restructuring and managing the finance department, applying new software and automating processes.

Yang Guoxiang, Finance Coordinator

January 2013 - November 2017

Responsible for overseeing, coordinating and administering the financial records, systems and processes of the company.

Valentini Lingerie, Co-Founder

January 2008 - November 2013

Managed all sales, including e-commerce sales.

EDUCATION

Frontend Developer Program, Sydney, AU, Generation - 2022

Full Stack Developer, Lisbon, PT, Ironhack - 2021

Master Business Administration, São Paulo, SP, Fundação Getúlio Vargas - 2020-2021

Bachelor of Business Administration, São Paulo, SP, FMU - 2014-2018

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: Portuguese and English

Certifications & Training: CS50's Introduction to Computer Science (coursera).